Step 1: click (969, 364) [OK]\NI can see the Amazon homepage with a 'Continue shopping' button in the center. However, I need to search for 'raspberry
Step 2: click (969, 364) [OK]\NI can see the Amazon homepage with a 'Continue shopping' button in the center. The previous action was a click at coordi
Step 3: find_and_click (1174, 192) [OK]\NI can see the Amazon homepage with a search bar at the top. The search box is located in the header area, to the right o
Step 4: click (390, 292) [OK]\NI can see the Amazon homepage with a search bar at the top. There's a modal dialog box in the center about shipping to J
Step 5: type  [OK]\NI can see the Amazon homepage with the search bar at the top. The search input field is visible in the header area. I ne
Step 6: key  [OK]\NI can see the Amazon homepage with various product categories displayed. Looking at the task history, I've already typed
Step 7: scroll  [OK]\NLooking at the screenshot, I can see an Amazon page with various product categories displayed. The previous task history
Step 8: scroll  [OK]\NLooking at the current screenshot, I can see an Amazon page displaying various product categories like 'Home Essentials'
Step 9: find_and_click (1167, 187) [OK]\NLooking at the current screenshot, I can see the Amazon homepage with a search bar at the top. The search bar is located
Step 10: key  [OK]\NLooking at the screenshot, I can see the Amazon homepage with the search bar at the top. The search input field is visib
Step 11: click (877, 177) [OK]\NLooking at the screenshot, I can see the Amazon homepage with the search bar at the top. The search input field is visib
Step 12: find_and_click (1174, 192) [OK]\NLooking at the current screenshot, I can see the Amazon homepage with the search bar at the top. The search bar is locat